http://www.expresschemist.co.uk/info/privacy-policy.html

top
CLOSE
An important message from Express Chemist
In these unprecedented times due to COVID-19 we are listening to the latest advice from the government and their health specialists. We are continuing to work in these challenging times so that we can serve the needs of our customers.
Please note that we are receiving a particularly high volume of orders, enquiries, telephone calls and emails. We are working exceptionally hard to process orders and respond to customer enquiries as quickly as possible. Unfortunately it is currently taking a little longer to process and dispatch orders than usual, so please allow 2-3 working days for shipment.
Please also note that postal services and couriers are experiencing similar challenges so please allow longer delivery times than usual. We would be grateful if you can be patient and not contact us regarding your order before these times are up so we can reduce the pressure on our customer service team.
Thank you for your patience and understanding.
If you have symptoms of coronavirus stay at home and self-isolate for 10 days.
For information about coronavirus please click here.
Keep well and stay safe.
This website uses cookies. By continuing to use this website you are giving consent to cookies being used. For more information please view our Privacy Policy.
0800 542 1203
GBP
GBP
EUR
USD
Register
My Account
Order Tracking
Stop Smoking
Sweating (Excessive)
Worms
Bestsellers
£1.95(incl VAT)
Ametop Gel 4% 1.5g
£3.95(incl VAT)
Epimax Cream 500g
Health
Health
General Health
Baby & Child
First Aid
By Area of the Body
Pet Health
Bestsellers
£1.95(incl VAT)
Ferrous Fumarate 322mg film-Coated 28 Tablets
£11.50(incl VAT)
Efamol Efalex 150ml Liquid
Baby & Child
Baby and Child Safety
Baby & Child Skin Care
Baby and Child Sundries
Breast Pumps
Chicken Pox
Child Sun Protection
Skin Conditions
Soothers (Dummies)
Teething
Warts and Verrucas
Worms
Bestsellers
£3.45(incl VAT)
Cow and Gate Instant Carobel 135g
£1.20(incl VAT)
Aptamil Pro Futuro First Infant Milk 200ml
First Aid
Antiseptics
Bandages
Blood Pressure Monitors
Cold Therapy
Disinfectants and Sterilisation
Dressings
Bestsellers
£1.95(incl VAT)
Ametop Gel 4% 1.5g
£0.55(incl VAT)
Mepore Dressing 11 x 15 cm
By Area of the Body
Blood & Heart
Ears
Eyes
Feet
Hair
Hands
Bestsellers
£1.95(incl VAT)
Ferrous Fumarate 322mg film-Coated 28 Tablets
£11.50(incl VAT)
Efamol Efalex 150ml Liquid
Pet Health
Pet Care
Cat Health
Dog Health
Fleas and Ticks
Pet Sundries
Pet Supplements
Worming
Bestsellers
£4.50(incl VAT)
Celluvisc 1% w/v Eye Drops Single Dose Containers 30
£11.50(incl VAT)
Efamol Efalex 150ml Liquid
Electrical Health
Batteries and Adaptors
Blood Glucose Meters
Blood Pressure Monitors
Electric Toothbrushes
Nebulisers and Steam Inhalers
Pedometers
Scales
TENS
Thermometers
Bestsellers
£1.00(incl VAT)
Kodak Extra Heavy Duty AA x 10
£8.75(incl VAT)
Accu-Chek FastClix Lancets 200+4
Condition
Condition
Baby Conditions
Ear Conditions
Eye Conditions
Hair Conditions
Health Conditions
Bestsellers
£1.00(incl VAT)
Healthpoint Spectacle wipes 50
£4.50(incl VAT)
Celluvisc 1% w/v Eye Drops Single Dose Containers 30
Hair Conditions
Balding
Dandruff
Hair Loss
Bestsellers
£1.95(incl VAT)
Xpel Medicated Shampoo 300ml
£8.50(incl VAT)
Oilatum Scalp Treatment Shampoo 100ml
Health Conditions
Allergies
Anaemia
Anaesthetics
Arthritis
Asthma
Bladder Weakness
Gluten Free Foods
Gum Disease (Gingivitis)
Hangover
Head Lice and Nits
Iron
Lice Infestation
Mouth Ulcers
Muscle Pain
Nail infection
Nasal Congestion
Smoking (Giving up)
Snoring Prevention
Sore Throat
Toothache
Bestsellers
A-Z Conditions
A - Z Conditions
Bestsellers
Vitamins
Bestsellers
£1.60(incl VAT)
Fortisip Bottle Strawberry 200ml
£1.10(incl VAT)
Numark Zinc 15mg 60 Tablets
Specialised Dietary Supplements
Women's Health
Men's Health Supplements
Baby and Child Supplements
Healthy Bones and Joints
Amino Acids
Heart and Circulation
Bestsellers
£1.60(incl VAT)
Fortisip Bottle Strawberry 200ml
£1.10(incl VAT)
Numark Zinc 15mg 60 Tablets
Beauty
Beauty
Beauty
Grooming
Beauty
Anti-Ageing
Body Lotion
Bestsellers
£1.00(incl VAT)
Pearl Drops Smokers Stain Removing Whitening Gel 50ml
£1.00(incl VAT)
Tea Tree Foaming Face Wash 200ml
Grooming
Bathing Accessories
Electric Toothbrushes
Emery Boards
Epilators
Hair Care
Hair Spray and Mousse
Bestsellers
£1.00(incl VAT)
Pearl Drops Smokers Stain Removing Whitening Gel 50ml
£1.00(incl VAT)
Tea Tree Foaming Face Wash 200ml
Perfumes
Perfumes
Fragrances
Fragrances
All Fragrances A - Z
Fragrances For Men
Fragrances For Her
Classic Fragrances
Bestsellers
£2.50(incl VAT)
David Beckham Homme Shower Gel 200ml
£2.40(incl VAT)
David Beckham Homme Deodorant Spray 150ml
Toiletries
Toiletries
Daily Essentials
Daily Essentials
Antibacterial Wipes
Bathing Accessories
Bath Salts
Bestsellers
£1.10(incl VAT)
Medipure Medicated Body Powder 200g
£1.40(incl VAT)
Morny French Fern Talc 100g
Prescriptions
Currency (GBP)
GBP
EUR
USD
Register
Login
Order Tracking
Enter Search Terms
Search
null
Main Privacy Policy
Express Chemist Privacy Policy This privacy policy sets out how Express Chemist uses and protects any information that you give Express Chemist when you use this website. Express Chemist is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Express Chemist may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 13/02/2018. What we collect We may collect the following information:
name and job title contact information including email address demographic information such as postcode other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Links to other websites Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. Controlling your personal information You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us or emailing us at info@expresschemist.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Express Chemist, Gateway House, Wallis Avenue, Maidstone, Kent, ME15 9NE, United Kingdom. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Click here if you have a general query that is not covered by the above options Return to the main help page Start shopping at Express Chemist now
Express Chemist Gateway House, Wallis Avenue, Maidstone, Kent, ME15 9NE
Phone (UK) 0800 542 1203Phone (International) +44 (0) 1622 763 434
Subscribe to our Newsletter
Get the latest offers and product news
Enter Email Address
